tinyhousepins.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy, Disclaimer, Usage Policy & DMCA Policy – Tiny House Pins

TinyHousePins.com Privacy Policy

We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use TinyHousePins.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.

TinyHousePins.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers’, consumers’ and online visitors’ privacy on our website.

Personal Information

TinyHousePins.com collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number.

This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.

Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties.

Use of Cookies and Web Beacons

We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site’s services, a cookie enables TinyHousePins.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.

A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.

We may serve third-party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web site to ascertain how many times you’ve seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on our web site.

Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google, which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uses the DART cookie, which enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Web. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn’t cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.

Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act

This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.

Non-Personal Information

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

Release of Information

If TinyHousePins.com is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.

How You Can Correct or Remove Information

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please click on this link and/or use our Contact Us page.

Legal

The information and other content within this website are provided for entertainment purposes only and should not be considered advice. While all information shared here is believed to be accurate, the owner(s) and operator(s) of this website disclaim all warranties expressed, implied or statutory, regarding the accuracy, timeliness, and/or completeness of the information contained within these pages. Please seek advice from a qualified professional before doing anything.

Third Party Affiliate Links

TinyHousePins.com is an affiliate with some of the companies whose products are occasionally mentioned, linked to and recommended on this site. This allows us to earn commissions for sales generated through this website without any extra cost on your part. This, along with advertising, helps support our efforts while helping you find solutions.

DMCA Policy

TinyHousePins.com and Tiny House Media LLC are in compliance with 17 U.S.C. * 512 and the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA). Our policy is to respond to any infringement notices and take appropriate actions under the DMCA and other applicable intellectual property laws.

If your copyrighted material has been posted on TinyHousePins.com and you want this material removed, you must provide a written communication that details the information listed in the following section. Please be aware that you will be liable for damages (including potential court costs and attorneys’ fees) if you misrepresent information listed on our site that is infringing on your copyrights.

The following elements must be included in your copyright infringement claim:

– You must provide evidence of the authorized person to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

– You must provide sufficient contact information so that we may contact you. Please include a valid email address, phone number and mailing address.

– You must identify in sufficient detail the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed.

– You must provide a statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.

– You must provide a statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

– The letter must be signed by the authorized person to act on behalf of the owner, or the owner itself, of the exclusive right that is allegedly being infringed.

You can send the infringement notice to the address below:  
DMCA Registered Agent  
Tiny House Media LLC  
300 5TH AVE S #332  
Naples, FL 34102  
United States

Or send an electronic copy to:  
tinyhousemedia@gmail.com

Once the proper bona fide infringement notification is received by the Designated Agent it is company policy to do the following:

– Remove or disable access to the allegedly infringing material

– To notify the content provider, user, member, or other contributor that the material has been removed or disabled

– Repeat offenders (content providers, users, members, or other contributors) will have the infringing material removed from the system and the company will terminate the content provider’s access to contributing.

Updates and Effective Date

TinyHousePins.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.

Agreeing to Terms

If you do not agree to TinyHousePins.com’s Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.
